childsplayclothing.co.uk 2014-07-06

# Privacy Policy

Effective 24th November 2008

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

Name  
Address  
Phone Number

We use a third party payment gateway to process payments on this web site. This means we never store your credit or debit card details anywhere in our database. This information is collected by the payment processor and used for the purposes of processing your transaction.

### Personal information

We value our customers, and our priority is to ensure your personal information is secure and your privacy is respected. We collect customer information when you place an order online, in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products and promotions. In addition, you may elect to sign up to receive email updates about our products and promotions.  
We collect personal information only when you voluntarily submit the information and we most definitely do not sell or rent the information you provide to us to third parties. When you make an online purchase from us, we use your information to process your order. We will also send you emails to confirm your order, and we may need to contact you by telephone, email or regular post if we have other questions regarding your order.  
If at any time you would like us to remove you from our email mailing list or registration database, please contact us via email, including your full name and the email address used when accessing or ordering from our site.  
We may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These web sites have their own policies regarding privacy, which you should review before visiting them. We have no responsibility for linked web sites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

###   
Payment security

We use the SagePay Payment Service Provider system. All transaction information passed between merchant sites and the SagePay systems are encrypted using 128-bit SSL certificates. Sounds complicated, we know. You can feel secure in the knowledge that nothing you pass to the SagePay servers can be examined, used or modified by third parties attempting to gain access to sensitive information. Your details are not disclosed to any third parties without your consent. For more information please visit [www.sagepay.com](http://www.sagepay.com/).

### Email Marketing and Newsletters Opt-in and Opt-out

When you register an account with us, you will be given the option to opt-out of subscribing to newlsetter service. Our newsletter service provides you with email alerts for new products, discounts, sale products, contests, new brands and other items of interest.

We do not sell or otherwise pass your details to third parties for marketing purposes. Marketing communications you subscribe to will only be sent by Childsplay Clothing  
At all times, we will offer you the opportunity to unsubscribe out of any service or update to which you have subscribed, if you change your mind. Any e-mail we send you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of that particular mailshot. Simply follow the indications in the e-mail. Alternatively you can change your email preferences or opt out of all emails by logging into My Account.  
Alternatively, to opt out of any direct mail service or updates, please contact our customer care team on +44 (0)20 8514 5007 or by email.

### Cookie policy

Childsplay Clothing uses 'cookies' to give you the best, most personal experience. It allows us to provide you important services, such as remembering your preferences. Using our website means you're okay with this.  
You can opt-out or opt-in use of 3rd-party cookies on our website by clicking the following link: [opt-out 3d-party cookies](http://www.childsplayclothing.co.uk.com/privacy/).

### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and track visitor behaviour.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in using your email address and password that you set when you registered.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by logging in and making changes, or you can contact us and we can make those changes for you.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, or if you wish for us to remove your data from our systems please contact us or email directly to info @ childsplayclothing.co.uk.
